
Created by : Titanium Steel

==Controls==
  Player 1 =
Left and Right to move.
Up to use the powerup.
Hold space to activate Ghost Mode, press up or down to noclip.
  Player 2 =
A and D to move.
W to use the powerup.
Hold E to activate Ghost Mode, press W or A to noclip.

==Story of Creation==
I created this when i was bored, but left it unfinished and never remembered it until a few days later
when i was bored and checking out my Scratch games. I found this, unfinished state. I decided since it 
was my birthday when i found the game, i wanted to share my scratch games i made with you all.
Thanks for playing.

==Credits==
Developer, Designer, Programmer, and etc. : Titanium Steel (Me)
The Reason I Was So Good In Scratch : Josegaming
Testers : Titanium Steel (Me)

==Change Log==
1.00 - The Big Bang : Release
1.10 - Power Up! : Added power ups "Gun" and "Boots" and added the README file.
1.12 - Challanges : Added zombies, leaping walls, the challange mode, and the change log.
1.15 - The Family Friendly(?) Game : Added the abillity to shoot zombies, added the usernames with the inabillity to type vulgar words, 
guns now can turn left or right and slightly modified the music, usernames also are attached with scores
in the Leaderboard, added the abillity to reset your username and the whole progress of the game.
1.20 - Bug and Insects : An extremely buggy update that will never be released. I think.
1.22 - Two Chapters : There are two types. a and b.
a= 
Added the console and fixed the bug where the player can type inappopriate names in the player's
username by typing it twice or playing while the username box is still on. Added also default or random
names if the player didn't set an username yet.
b=
Fixed the bug where walls spawn inside the floor after the score 5 and the bug if the player is killed,
the score in the leaderboard doesn't contain an username.
1.29 - Forgotten Memories : Unknown
1.34 - God of War: Added Arlokh and the username easter eggs.
1.39 - Debuggers : Added the debug mode and fixed some bugs.
1.40 - The More the Merrier : Added multiplayer mode (might be buggy). Technically a beta version, but it's already stable enough to be called full.
1.45 - Anti Cheat : Fixed the bug where if the multiplayer mode wasn't even on, when the player dies, the leaderboard and the game doesn't appear and stops and fixed the bug that the zombie was stuck in the edge after passing through a line. Also removed the 1 and 2 score function to install anti cheat security and placed a password for the set score command. Gave versions names. Added a new command that does rwkoriwidsidwkdsdwidsod. Added an extremely rare easter egg.
1.50 - B4N 5P1K35 4 L1F3 : Fixed a load of bugs, removed the spikes entirely.
1.53 - Beethovem : Changed the music and added some commands. Added a cooldown for the Ghost Mode.

Version : 1.53